I think the fire chief wants to introduce Gerard first, before Gerard does the invocation force.
I would like to get all the major Gerard Dahlsville in the United States, the associate pastor of the first prison church.
He was the youth minister for almost 12 years.
He's got two children who want to go into those art prison college and drop those dollars.
Going to my home high school here to change Gerard's wife's school future.
And he is taking us on the work that has helped us with being our chaplain.
Awesome.
Do I really appreciate you supporting the fire department in that way?
It really means a pot.
Do you want to say the blessing?
Okay.
Lord, we thank you so much for this day and for the opportunity to acknowledge your presence and what we're asking for your blessing on these next moments with this group.
Lord, do you have been wisdom?
Just watch over our community, I pray you're blessing on each individual that's in this room.
Whether out front or behind the scenes, or the youth, less their families, as they sacrifice so much for our community that you would just watch over them and protect them.
Lord, we pray that as they give so much to our community that they would know how much they're appreciated by all of its members.
I pray that again, do you just even have wisdom as any decisions?
And Lord, just to be less their proceedings, say it's a do you sing with prayer?
Do you have it?
I do.
Lewis, I chose.
Aye.
Eight is good.
New business.
Dean or anyone?
No.
Nine is staff reports.
They're written reports.
You're packet available and staff is available if there are any questions.
Or none.
Ten is trustee community announcements.
Do you have any announcements that we need to make?
And the 11 is a German.
Do we have most to adjourn?
Motion.